[
    {
        "question": "MgO + HCl .................... + ........................",
        "options": [
            " MgH,CL2",
            "MgCl ,H2",
            "MgOH +CL2",
            "MgCl , H20"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "SO+ .............................. NaSO + HO",
        "options": [
            "NaOH",
            "NaCl",
            "NaO"        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "CHCOOH is a ................... ",
        "options": [
            "Weak acid",
            "Strong acid",
            "Strong base",
            "Weak base"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Oxide of non metal + base  ...................... + ...........................",
        "options": [
            "Salt + Hydrogen",
            "Hydrogen + Water",
            "Salt + Water",
            "Hydrogen + Metal"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In Neutralisation .............. and ............. is formed.",
        "options": [
            "Salt, Hydrogen",
            "Salt, Water",
            "Hydrogen, Oxygen",
            "Hydrogen, Water"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The ion present in NaOH",
        "options": [
            "Na+,Cl-",
            "Na+, OH-",
            "H+, OH-",
            "H+, Cl-"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question" : "The electrode connected to the negative terminal of battery",
        "options": [
            "Anode",
            "Cathode",
            "Tapode",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The Basic radical in KSO is",
        "options": [
            "K+",
            "SO4",
            "Ca2+",
            "H+"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Acidic radical in CaCl is",
        "options": [
            "Na+",
            "Ca2+",
            "Cl-",
            "Br-"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Number of H ion in HPO is ",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "HCl + NaOH ................... + .........................",
        "options": [
            "NaH, H2O",
            "NaCl, Na,H",
            " NaCl, H2O",
            "No reaction"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Metal oxide + dil HCl ...................... + ............................",
        "options": [
            "Salt, Hydrogen",
            "Salt, Hydroxyl",
            "Salt, Water",
            "Salt, Chorine"
        ],
        "answer":3 
    },
    {
        "question": "Acid are one which contain ....................... as the basic radical",
        "options": [
            "K+",
            "Ca2+",
            "H+",
            "Cl-"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Chorine has the tendency to ................. electron",
        "options": [
            "Gain",
            "Lose",
            "Both gain and lose",
            "Share"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Metal reacts with acid to liberate",
        "options": [
            "Chlorine",
            "Hydrogen",
            "Nitrogen",
            "Oxygen"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "PH of tooth paste is",
        "options": [
            "7",
            "8",
            "9.5",
            "10.5"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Number of OH ion is Al(OH) is",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The electrode connected to the positive terminal of battery is known",
        "options": [
            "Anode",
            "Cathode",
            "Tapode",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sodium have the tendency to ......................... electron",
        "options": [
            "Gain",
            "Lose",
            "Both gain and lose",
            "Share"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Acid and base react together to form salt and water is ............... reaction.",
        "options": [
            "Combination",
            "Decomposition",
            "Neutralization",
            "Displacement"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Number of H+ ions in CH3COOH is",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "PH of Vinegar is ",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    }
]